kenpom.com 2017-07-29

# kenpom.com privacy policy

The website located at https://www.kenpom.com ("Website") is owned and operated by Ken Pomeroy (the "Company"). We created this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and your personally identifiable information on our Website. 

This Policy is based on the principles of notice/awareness, choice/consent, access/participation and integrity/security in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities on the Website. In this document "You" shall refer to you, the end user of this site, whether as an individual, entity, company, organization or related. "We", the "Website", and/or the "Company", refers to the information, services, and other provisions by the Company, or located at the Website, or by individuals and entities associated with the Website. 

**_I. NOTICE OF OUR POLICY_**

This Policy notifies you of, among other things: (i) what information we gather from you, (ii) how we may use or disclose that information, (iii) with whom the information may be shared, (iv) what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information, (v) our efforts to protect the information, and (vi) how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information you provide to us. Please read this Policy carefully. 

**_II. WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION ARE COLLECTED AND WHY_**

a. 

_Information Submitted by You_

We do not request you to submit any information to the Website. Any communications, emails, or other information submitted by You to the website, or individuals related to the site is solely at your own election. The website has no responsibility or other obligation to store, maintain, respond or otherwise with respect to the information transmitted to the Website by you. You will be contacted by us only if you have expressly requested us to do so. 

b. 

_Information Collected by Cookies_

Currently the Website does not use "cookies", however we may, at some time either now or in the future, make use of website "cookies" to help you use our services more easily, specifically to collect information such as IP addresses, time spent on our Website (for software application specific web pages), and to help us continuously improve our Website and our services to you ("Data"). A "cookie" is a small data file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer to help our Website "remember" information about you to make it easier and more efficient for you to use our Website. Our Website may employ session cookies. A session cookie does not remain on your computer after you close your web browser window. Our session cookies contain none of your personal information and cannot be used to track you around the Internet. Our session cookies can only be used by this Website and they only exist for the duration of your visit. Depending on the settings in your browser, you may have the option to deny the session cookie; however, doing so may negatively impact upon the performance of the Website or restrict us in better serving your needs and interests. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

**_III. HOW DOES THE COMPANY USE MY INFORMATION?_**

a. 

_Use of Your Information_

Any information supplied by you is used to improve your experience, process and personalize your requests, improve the Website, develop new features, for support, and may be used for other purposes as stated herein. We may also use the information to show you a history of your activity, to provide you with statistics about you or your use of our product or service, or to provide you with a better user experience. The information collected may also be used to provide relevant advertisements, promotional messages and materials, or any other way as the Company deems fit. We may also retain your Data on a secure server and use this information in an aggregated form to measure number of visits, average time spent on the Website, pages viewed, and other relevant statistics. The Company also collects this information to measure the use of the Website and to improve the content of the Website. 

b. 

_Disclosure of Your Information_

The information we collect will only be collected upon your consent to this privacy policy. We may share your information with certain third parties. These third parties will be contractually bound to treat your information in accordance with this privacy policy. The Company reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when the Company believes that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of the Company, and/or to comply with any judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena, or legal process served upon the Company. 

c. 

_Managing Your Information_

You are entitled to removal of your Data from our database upon request. You may request us to correct, modify or delete all of your Data collected by us through the Website, by making such a request or a related inquiry by sending an email to ratings at kenpom.com. Unless you require us to delete your Data, we will keep your information for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Policy and for us to keep appropriate archives for our business operations. 

d. 

_Anonymous Data Collection_

We may anonymize and aggregate data from your usage of the Website to obtain or provide general statistics regarding the use of the Website and its specific features and functionalities that you use. 

**_IV. WHAT THE COMPANY DOES TO KEEP THE WEBSITE SECURE?_**

a. 

_Security_

The Company employs procedural and technical safeguards to secure the Website against misuse. Regardless of the precautions taken by us we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

**_V. ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY_**

By using this Website, you agree to this Website Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes shall take effect immediately upon their posting on our Website. Your continued use of Website or acceptance of emails following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy shall mean that you accept any and all such changes.
